backand.com 2017-05-15

# Backand Privacy Policy - Build scalable serverless applications with AWS Lambda

Back& (also referred to as: backand) is a powerful back-office Software, invented by MODUBIZ LTD (“MODUBIZ”), which serves as a Service (SaaS) platform for Apps. Adopting the service eliminates the need to code a Back-Office, saving a great deal of time and money. Back& plugs to any type of app and automatically generates a robust Back-Office application in no time.

### Introduction

At MODUBIZ we respect your right for privacy and protect any personal information that you may share with us, in an appropriate manner. We are committed to protect the privacy of individuals who register to use our Services (as defined below) (“Customers”), as well as individuals who visit our website (www.backand.com) (“Visitors”). The provisions within this notice apply to Customers and Visitors both past and present. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices in relation to the use of our Site and the related applications (the “Services”). As a condition to use of the Services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy as it may be updated from time to time. This Privacy Policy applies to www.backand.com (the “Site”) and all additional sites MODUBIZ provides its services from. Our unique cloud service enables our Customers to generate a robust Back-Office application, however, we do not control our Customers’ collection and use of data and their use of the information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies.

### Information Collected

When expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Services or registering to use the Services, we require you to provide us with your personal information, such as name, e-mail address, website URL, connection string to the database and phone number (“Personal Information” or “Customers’ Data”). You do not have a legal obligation to provide us any Personal Information, however, failure to provide such information or part of it, may prevent us from providing you with some of our services. We will have access to third party personal information provided by you as part of using our Services such as personal information about your users and/or their submissions to you. This information may include third party names, email addresses, phone numbers and physical addresses and will be used for business purposes only, such as processing the feedback information, and providing customer service.

### Use of Information Collected

The Personal Information we collect is only accessible to us and our affiliates, service providers and business partners (“Affiliated Third Parties”) and is not disclosed to any non-Affiliated Third Parties. The Personal Information is only used as expressly described in this Privacy Policy, for the purposes of providing the Services to you, Service improvement or for aggregate statistics about our Customers. We may also use the Customers’ Data for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in the Services and to send you information regarding the Company, its affiliates, and its partners, such as information about promotions or events.

### Cookies

From time to time, we may place information on your website computer to allow it to identify you. This information is commonly referred to as ‘cookies’. By showing how and when you use the Site and the Site Applications. This information can and is only used by MODUBIZ to improve the Site and the Site Applications on a continual basis. We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites utilize them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your browser to do so, if your browser so permits.

### Visitors’ Details

We use the Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone, operating system and other Visitors’ details collected in our log files to analyze the trends, administer the Site, and track Visitors’ movements and to improve our Site.

### Usage Details

Your usage details such as time, frequency, duration and pattern of use, features used and the amount of storage used will be recorded by us in order to enhance your experience of the Services and to help us provide you the best possible service.

### Data History

We store and maintain files, documents, to-do lists, emails and other data stored in your user account at our facilities in Israel. Subject to your prior consent to join our Data History Services and in order to prevent loss of data due to errors or system failures we also keep backup copies of data including the contents of your user account. Hence your files and data may remain on our servers even after deletion or termination of your user account. We assure you that the contents of your user account will not be disclosed to anyone and will not be accessible even to employees of MODUBIZ except in circumstances specifically mentioned in this Privacy Policy. We also do not process the contents of your user account for serving targeted advertisements.

### Sharing of information collected

We may need to disclose Personal Information to our affiliates, service providers and business partners solely for the purpose of providing the Services to you. For example, we may need to share Personal Information for customer relationship management purposes. In such cases MODUBIZ will also ensure that such affiliates, service providers and business partners comply with this Privacy Policy and adopt appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personal Information regarding visitors and users with our business partners and advertisers. Unless described in this Privacy Policy, we not share, sell, rent, or trade any Personal Information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

### Financial Information

In case of Services requiring payment, we require you to provide us with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number or other payment account information (“Financial Information”), which will be used solely for processing payments. Financial Information required for processing payment and future payment will be stored using common security methods designed for storing such information.

### Compelled Disclosure

Please be aware that laws in various jurisdictions in which we operate may obligate us to disclose Personal Information and the contents of your user account with regulatory authorities or as otherwise required by applicable law. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests. In addition, we may also disclose Personal Information and contents of your user account to law enforcement authorities if such disclosure is determined to be necessary by MODUBIZ in our sole and absolute discretion for protecting the safety of our users, employees, or the general public.

### Communications preferences

We offer Visitors and Customers who provide contact information a means to choose how we use the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of ModiBiz marketing e-mails. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to their account with MODUBIZ or the Services.

### Security

We adopt industry appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your Personal Information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in your user account. Access to your name and email address is restricted to our employees who need to know such information in connection with providing the Services to you and are bound by confidentiality obligations. You are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of your MODUBIZServices\ usernames and passwords.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

Any changes to the Privacy Policy Statement will be posted on our Site in order to keep you informed of any changes in nature of information collected, manner of collection, use and sharing of information . If you are concerned about how your Personal Information is used, you should check back at www.backand.com/privacy-policy, periodically.

### Contacting us

We make every effort, including periodic reviews to ensure that Personal Information provided by you is used in conformity with this Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns regarding our adherence to this Privacy Policy or the manner in which Personal Information is used for the purpose of providing the Services, kindly contact MODUBIZ’s Customer Support Services at support@backand.com. We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also co-operate with regulatory authorities in this regard if needed.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding these Terms of Use please contacts us at: [team@backand.com](mailto:team@backand.com)
